So folks are like totally cool with Israelis saying we deserve to take Palestinian land because
3,000 years ago we used to live here but black people saying we deserve reparations because
y'all had our people enslaved for 400 years during which time you did heinous scientific
experiments on black women you fed black babies to alligators y'all even drank out of the
skulls of slaves and stuffed your pillows with the hair of slaves then for another yeah like 70 80
years after that you enslaved us in prisons and in apartheid and prevented us from being able to own
land and homes etc big on the etc so is that is that what is that is that how it should go for for
israel there's no statute of limitations but for us times run out you tell me because all the money
that's being sent over there could actually be used to provide reparations in a number of ways
right here it'd actually be really good for the economy but that's another conversation for another
time that most of you all simply do not want to have you damn rude eh